quickhire.com 2003-06-01

# Welcome to QuickHire

**QuickHire Privacy Policy**

**Information Collection and Use**  
QuickHire® is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share or rent this information to any third party for any reason. QuickHire may use your personal information only to communicate with you regarding your requests and inquiries. 

**Logging and Tracking**  
When you visit the Web site, QuickHire receives and records information on its server logs from your browser, including IP Address, cookies information and requested pages. This usage information helps us to evaluate how our visitors and registered users use and navigate the Web site on an aggregate basis, including the number and frequency of visitors and registered users to each web page, and the length of their visits. This information is not linked to any identifiable personal information and is not shared with any third party for any reasons. 

**Security**  
This website takes every precaution to protect users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, their information is protected both online and offline. When user submit information on the Request a Demo form that information is encrypted and is protected. As previously stated, we do not sell, share or rent this information to any third party. 

**Links**  
The QuickHire website contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. Read the privacy statements of each website that collects identifiable information. 

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for QuickHire. If you have any questions or comments regarding this policy, please contact us. 

|  |  |   
---  
|   
U.S. Mint saves a fortune with QuickHire.  
**More**    
   
See our client list  
   
---  
| 

**QuickHire can create** different access levels allowing as many people as needed to be part of the hiring review process. 

**QuickHire easily works** with other systems such as background search companies, voice response, HRIS and HRMS. 

**QuickHire eliminates** virtually all time consuming paper handling. It can automatically respond to candidates, track their progress through the hiring process, and archive all records for future use.
